Thank you for watching!
Here you go! It's starting!
It's time for the "Halo! This time we have with us Rio Sakurai from Morning Musume 24 and Akari Endo from Juice Juice.
Akari Endo from JuiceJuice!
Please bear with us until the end of the show.
Please bear with me until the end.
So, although we are in different groups, we joined the same group at the same time.
We joined the same group at the same audition time.
Yay!
We don't have many chances to work together like this.
We joined together at the audition on June 29th, exactly two years ago.
Although we are in different groups
Although we are in different groups, our singing and dancing are so graceful and beautiful.
I am always inspired by them.
I am also inspired by your beautiful facial expressions.
I am also inspired by their beautiful expressions, and I will do my best this year.
Wow, that makes me so happy!
I'm going to make it my goal.
I know that we have opportunities to work together at Hello Project concerts and other events, so I hope we can continue to work together.
Let's have dinner together in the future.
Let's have dinner together.
Please do.
Yes, Morning Musume。 24 has started the concert tour "Spring More Morning Musume。 started on March 16th.
This is the first solo concert since Mizuki Fukumura's graduation.
There will be a lot of song assignments and dance positions and formations.
There were many changes in the song assignments, dance positions, formations, and so on.
I think this tour has led to the growth of each member.
And I personally worked hard on the dance for one of the songs.
And I think it's a very easy song to understand.
If you've been on the tour at least once, you may be able to recognize it.
I'm dancing a lot to a certain song, so please look forward to it as well.
I hope you'll come and see us.
Also, there are some songs that are bought differently on the tour.
I would be very happy if you could come and look forward to seeing which pattern will be followed on the tour you are going on.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, JuiceJuice's concert tour 2024 One Line will start this weekend.
This tour is the last tour for our leader, Akari Uemura, who is graduating.
I'm really looking forward to seeing Ms. Uemura during her performance, and I'm sure all the fans are looking forward to seeing her as well.
I would like to see Ms. Uemura during her performance, and I would also like all the fans to have her in their hearts and eyes.
I have set a goal to work hard on my dance this year, so I hope to see my dance grow as well.
I'm looking forward to seeing how my dancing is growing as well.
We'll be touring together, and we'll be performing at the Nippon Budokan for the final leg of the tour.
Morning Musume。24 will perform on May 27th, and JuiceJuice?
On June 14.
So I hope you will all come to see the final show.
Please check out this video.
Here you go.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
There are no rules in love.
You think of me, I think of you, that's all that matters
You'll never have a deeper moment
Let's go all in
That's it, that's it, that's it
With a partner of wonder
with the talk of tender feelings
I'll give you a little help, you know...
I'm so happy in my spare time
I've been in love with you for a long time
Gently raise your hand and say...
What do you do?
What are you going to do?
I can't get through to you
When I've already asked you out, it's almost time to go
Help me with your right hand.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Daffs, daffs, daffs
Where does love come from?
If it's a distant parent, it's you
Daffy daffy daffy daffy
When I was in love with you I always hated you
Because you said this is my youth
That's it, that's it, that's it
When night falls and love ceases
I'm really scared.
I'm really scared... of what I'll see.
A little weakness will fall on your face
I'll go crazy and run around
I'll ride and run and run
It's more than that, it's over
You'll always be
Going my way
It's a celestial body that's passing
Already a glowing notice
A bundle of sound
Help me with your right hand
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Help me, Lord Buddha
Ouch, ouch, ouch
It's he who I want to love
I can't see what's in his heart
It's the other's help
I'm the one with the looks
Show them
When it comes to love, love, love
Leave it to the love magistrate
One more time, it won't happen again
I can't take the plunge
That's it, that's it, that's it
by having a colorful face
I'm stretching my tender feelings
I'm yo-yoing
She threw a little passion
She said it's like eggs
Gather up Luzhin's little dicks.
What are you gonna do?
Tweeting about your trance.
It's on your mind.
Wow, when in doubt
You teach me what you mean
I'll pass on the glowing tone
Teach me what you mean
And we'll move on
And that's the end of the matter
Doli plates
I'm sure you'll be fine, just as you always are.
Thank you for watching!
This episode is brought to you by Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 24 and Akari Endo of JuiceJuice。
Akari Endo of JuiceJuice.
Yes, we'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
Yay!
I'm going to ask you a few questions.
So let's answer in a quick tempo without thinking too much!
Okay, I'll do my best.
What are you into these days?
Yogurt and knitting.
JuiceJuice is releasing a new single on May 15!
What is the best word for this single?
Freedom
Hmmm...
What are you doing to prepare for the tour starting this weekend?
I want to do some muscle training.
What's the best ice cream you've had recently?
Soft ice cream at an antenna store in Hokkaido.
What kind of person do you want to be in the future?
It's been two years since I joined JuiceJuice.
I would like to be a person who can support JuiceJuice.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to talk about something that's been bothering me.
JuiceJuice is releasing a new single on May 15.
You mentioned that the perfect word for this single is freedom.
Why is this?
Akari Uemura, the leader of JuiceJuice, has made freedom her motto.
Akari Uemura, the leader of JuiceJuice, has been leading JuiceJuice with freedom as her motto.
I feel that freedom is overflowing from the various music videos.
I'm looking forward to it!
I hope you are looking forward to the music videos, the new songs, and the performances.
I'm looking forward to watching a lot of music videos.
And the best ice cream I had recently was
Antenna store.
I guess you mean an antenna store in Tokyo?
Yes, they sell a lot of Hokkaido products, even the most fanatical ones.
I went to an antenna store.
I went to the antenna shop, and someone there recommended it to me.
I eat soft-serve ice cream without being told that it is delicious.
The soft-serve ice cream I had there was quite rich.
The soft serve ice cream I had there was so rich and tasted like the milk itself.
It was like having it rolled up in a cone like you would get at a restaurant and eating it right then and there.
It's not often that you can have it wrapped around a cone and eat it on the spot like you can at a restaurant.
That's for sure.
I was really happy.
I'm a little bit addicted to antenna stores, so whenever I see one, I tend to go in.
I had just heard that there was a Hokkaido antenna store in Yurakucho, Tokyo.
So when I heard about it, I thought, "What an antenna store!
So please take me with you next time and tell me what you recommend in Hokkaido!
I want to teach you a lot!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Questions for Rio-chan will be asked after the VTR.
Hello! I'm always wanting to sleep.
I don't have anything I don't have anything I want to sleep with you always you know
So vague
Juice Juice News Single Naimono Love
May 15 Onside
Haloste!
Next I would like to ask Rio-chan some questions.
I'll do my best.
You're always in style, Rio-chan.
I wore a refreshing blue top for the warmer weather.
What are you most interested in now?
I graduated from high school and I want to continue my studies, so I'm thinking of taking a certification test.
The final concert of your tour will be held at Nippon Budokan on May 27.
What have you left out of the Nippon Budokan concert so far?
I think I didn't arrange my hair, which I don't do very often.
What do you pay special attention to in your makeup?
Tear troughs.
What is your current challenge as Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 What do you want to challenge yourself as Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。
I want to measure my memory capacity.
Oh!
I'd like to ask you a question that just caught my attention.
What kind of challenge would you like to take on as a memory capper?
Morning Musume。 Morning Musume has a lot of songs.
I've been a member for 2 years now.
There are so many songs that I don't remember anymore.
I wonder if I can remember all the songs.
It's fun to be able to memorize songs, and at the same time
At the same time, I want to test how good my memory is.
I want to learn more and more Morning Musume。 I wanted to learn more and more Morning Musume。
so I decided to go to this event.
I have memorized almost all of JuiceJuice's songs.
but I still have a lot of songs to learn after 2 years.
I am surprised that I still have a lot of songs to learn after 2 years.
I can see the memories of your hard work in every tour.
Thank you very much and I will do my best.
You mentioned tear troughs as one of the points of your makeup.
That's right.
I'm not good at making up tear troughs.
That's why I'm trying to learn a few tricks.
But I'm not very good at makeup either.
If you want, Akari is better than me.
Akari is much better at it than I am.
But I think that by drawing the tear troughs well, I can make the eyes look bigger and stronger.
I think it makes my eyes look bigger and more powerful.
Whenever I put on makeup, I always do this.
Whenever I do makeup, I always make sure to draw in the tear troughs that form when I laugh and smile.
I think that's the trick.
Also, when I go to a live performance, I put a little bit of sparkle on my face.
If you laugh a lot, you can get tear troughs.
If you smile a lot, you'll get tear troughs, and if you smile a lot, you'll get tear troughs.
If you smile a lot, you can get tear troughs.
Then let's laugh a lot.
Let's all laugh a lot.
Laugh a lot and make tear troughs.
I'm going to do my best on this weekend's tour.
Good luck!
Hallo! Stay tuned for more after this!
This is Natsuyaki Miyabi!
Here we go!
Hello Kitchen!
This time, we have a member here.
Yes, I'm Iroko, the tea lady.
Pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, I really like cooking.
I really like cooking, so I hope to learn a lot of things this time.
Yes, let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
Please take care of me, sir.
Yes, I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Now, what would you like to make this time?
Yes, this time I'll make a Madite scallop foie gras.
Foie gras.
Brezetoe with Chinese cabbage
Brezetoe
Stylish!
Ingredients?
I'll tell you what they are.
Yes, this way, sir.
Doctor, what is poele?
Poiret is a French cooking method.
In French, it's like a pot or a bowl or something like that.
In French, it's a pot or a bowl or something like that.
In the old days, they used to cook it in such a way.
It's just a remnant of that.
In modern times, poele is a way of cooking fish
Generally, fish is cooked slowly in butter or something like that.
It's like that.
And one more thing, the word "braisé" was introduced this time.
Bresse is similar to steaming.
I see.
That's why we sweat vegetables.
There's also "étouffée"...
It's difficult.
There's also étouffée.
I think it's easier to understand if it's called braisée.
I think it's better if it's called "steamed".
Let's cook until the end!
Thank you very much.
Now, what would you like to do first, doctor?
First of all, I brought a fillet of sea bream today.
A big one.
The bone is right here in the middle, so we'll take it out one by one.
Have you ever done this before?
No, I haven't!
It's a good experience.
It's not that easy.
The way I'm going to remove the bone, it's at this angle.
You have to pull it straight out in the opposite direction.
It's a little tricky.
Hard!
Oh! That's fun!
It just pops right out.
It's a lot of fun!
Definitely a little stressful!
It's gonna feel good.
That's a good one.
That's good.
You're good.
Really?
One or two cuts, and then you can cut right here.
Yes, sir.
Let's use the middle one.
Stand up a little.
Stand up.
Like this.
Like this. Like pulling a chopping board.
Yes! It's done!
The thing about grilling this fish is that the skin is tough.
The flesh is soft, so when you cook the skin, the skin shrinks
The flesh is soft, so if you cook the skin, the skin will shrink and the flesh will be pulled out with it.
I'll put a line here.
Yes. Should I stand it up?
If it's too vertical, it'll cut off the skin.
Like this.
Okay. Now put it in the fridge without wrapping it.
I'm going to make a boulezet of Chinese cabbage.
I've never cut Chinese cabbage before.
Really?
I don't cut bacon.
You've done it before? Yes, I have.
On the other hand, what do you often cut?
I cut a lot.
Do you cut things you help with?
I often cut carrots.
They're pretty hard.
Isn't that pretty hard?
It's my first time.
Carrots and onions?
I often use carrots because I like the taste.
I use carrots when I make my own food.
I like to peel them with a peeler.
I also like to cut them.
Then, I'd like to make a braise out of the Chinese cabbage I just cut up.
I'd like to make a braise.
First, put olive oil for 10 seconds.
Is it okay if I put it in?
Yes.
Now a little bit.
When it's soft...
All the tough bits over here.
Ta-da!
Salt helps the water out of the Chinese cabbage.
This is a side note.
You can make pasta with Chinese cabbage
You can make pasta with Chinese cabbage!
Wow!
You just put this in? Pasta. Pasta, yes.
The sauce is warm too.
Oh, that's good. This is good, too.
It goes well with cream, too.
It's getting clear.
Shall we add butter?
It's good with butter, isn't it?
Let's put it in. I'll try to catch it.
When the butter is melted, add a teaspoon of sugar.
Be careful, it burns easily.
Yes, sir.
And it's getting hot, so it's good.
Put in the leaves and mix quickly.
Here's the point of miyamizu!
Use a little water to make it sweat.
A little water or wine.
Not the amount you'd boil.
You're right. It's a very small amount.
And this...
But it's weak.
Cover it with a lid to make it sweat.
That's right, Chinese cabbage has a lot of moisture.
Moisture of the person himself.
Well, if there's nothing, it gets burned.
A little water just now.
The water evaporates into steam, and the lid stays on.
So the water doesn't evaporate... so it's steamed in here all the time.
Let's explore Rocco together with the teacher, shall we?
Let's explore with the doctor.
Yes, sir.
What about Rocco?
What's Rocco's latest obsession?
Or a secret you haven't told us yet.
But...
You have a lucky guy.
16 is a lot of secrets.
That's true.
Of course there are things you don't want to tell.
The ones you can tell.
The ones who can say something...
Like, "I'm secretly doing this...
But the other day, I was in Saga, and I'm from Saga.
I'm from Saga, and I went back home to Saga, and I played the game of life with my family.
It's nice, isn't it?
Yes, it's called Nanja Monja.
What's that?
What's this?
Yes, I said...
I don't know.
Let's ask him to tell us.
What the hell is that?
It's a card game with patterns.
There are about five cards, each with a certain pattern.
There are characters.
We name the characters ourselves.
Can it be anything? Name
Anything is fine.
Why did you name it?
I'm doing something.
Commonly used name
Hexago
What's that?
It really could be anything
Husband free
But you have a very close family.
Yes.
Saga.
It's a place I don't get to visit very often.
Yes.
Is it famous?
What?
What's it famous for?
I guess you'd have to say the yobuko squid.
The squid is called Yobuko.
Well, I've heard of it.
Yes, it is.
It's very famous.
The squid from there is very delicious.
Yes, it is.
Have you ever eaten it?
I didn't know that.
Yobuko?
It's called yobuko.
It's also written in Job... "the son of a child.
I didn't know that.
You're not a good cook.
You can use it next time.
You're right. It's yobuko squid.
Just mix it for a second
Stir, stir, stir.
Stir.
Here.
You know, cream.
Or pasta cooking water.
Yes, sir.
Oh, that looks good.
That's good, too.
Paksal pasta.
Oh, that's easy.
That's easy.
So far, so easy.
Let's have a taste.
Whoa.
Oh, yeah!
Is it okay? Is it salty?
A little salty...
But we'll wrap it up with some sauce or something later.
It's fine.
It's delicious.
Is it sweet? Yes, it's sweet.
It's very sweet.
That's all that matters.
What shall we do next?
We'll use rape blossoms and cormorants for decoration, but you can eat them raw too.
Cormorants don't work so well.
Only at this time of the year. March, April, three years old.
It's like drawing a picture or drawing a line with the tip of a pen.
Yes, you mix it with a little cold water with this and leave it at home, and it comes around.
The bottom part of the rape blossoms, you can drop this part here, and this part here, and this part here.
You need a little bit of thin skin, so if you don't take it off gently, it'll come out all over the place.
You are very dexterous.
Really? Puler is probably trained on carrots.
Yes, trained.
The rape itself doesn't have that much water, so just take off a little bit, put it in a bag, put it in the microwave for about 50 seconds and see what happens.
We'll have to touch the stems.
Oh, they're totally fine now.
And then we'll drop them in cold water.
Yes, so that's all for this time.
The next time will be the finished product, so please look forward to it!
Enjoy!
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye.
One more time, vigorously. Stop your body.
Yes, sir.
Perfect.
Bon appétit.
Delicious!
Next is the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
Hello Project has many wonderful lyrics.
Akari, do you have any lyrics that have touched your heart recently?
The song "Otona no Jijo" ("Adult Circumstances")
There's a lyric that says, "Don't take away my freedom because of adult circumstances.
When you go to school or work
I think there are times when you are dissatisfied with your teachers and so on.
Listen to this song and you'll feel better.
I think it will make you feel better.
I hope you will listen to this song when you are dissatisfied.
I hope you will listen to this song when you are dissatisfied with the way you want to do things.
I think there are times when people don't actually understand what I want to do
I think there are times when people deny it.
When I listen to these lyrics
I think it will give you a strong feeling that you won't be defeated by such things.
I also like the lyrics of this song very much, so I feel the same way.
Me too.
I'm going to talk about it in the VTR later on.
Please check it out!
Please watch it.
Presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of Hello! Project's songs and talk about the lyrics that touched your heart.
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the song. Project songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Rio Sakurai, will present the lyrics.
I'll show you.
Here it is!
DADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADAN
Tears are there for the last laugh
YES!
The song is called "I'm lucky girl" by Morning Musume。 I'm lucky girl" by Morning Musume。
I really think that this song is one that you can listen to as if you were the main character.
Especially when I first heard the lyrics, "Tears are for laughing at the end," I thought to myself, "Yes, that's true.
I thought, "Yes, that's right.
You don't have to force yourself not to shed tears.
I thought that if I shed tears, the result of my efforts would come to fruition.
I thought about that when I listened to this song.
I like to listen to this song on the way home when I'm feeling a little down, to lift my spirits.
I often sing this song alone at karaoke bars.
I feel like I'm the main character when I sing this song alone.
There are other lyrics, such as "todoroke" and so on.
There are some phrases that you don't find in other lyrics.
I love this song so much that I listened to the lyrics.
I love this song because it really makes me feel strong.
It makes me feel that I can believe in myself.
I don't know... it's not like I'm a little drunk or anything.
I'm here, but I'm here, but I'm here...
I totally understand.
I feel like I can be strong just by listening to it.
I think that's really cool.
I think you can feel the quality of the song more when you play it live.
I feel like it brightens up the stage at once.
I was still in the set rhythm of the MMM tour.
I'd like to play it too, since I didn't get to do it.
Don't you think I'm a little bit in love with the main character of this song?
He says, "Just follow me.
Like, "Oh, you want me to follow you? Like that.
I do too.
What do you think? What about you, Haruka?
I've seen the video before.
I've never really thought about the meaning of the song after listening to it alone.
But now that you've introduced the song in this way, written in text only...
I would like to listen to the song again, paying attention to the lyrics.
I'm sure you will.
I'm sure there are some fans who would like to listen to the song after reading the lyrics again.
Maybe some of you might want to listen to the song after seeing the lyrics again.
I hope you'll pay attention to the lyrics as well!
So please look forward to the next episode!
Enjoy!
Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 24's Rio Sakurai and
Akari Endo of JuiceJuice will be presenting "Halo! STE!
Project stream from the day after tomorrow, April 19, on the Halo! Project stream.
Project Hina Fest 2024 Project Hina Fest 2024
JuiceJuice&Beyond Premium
Tsubaki Factory & Ochanomoto Premium will start streaming!
Now that the streaming has started, we'd like to take this opportunity to thank all of our fans who were unable to make it.
Project HinaFest 2024 JuiceJuice&Beyond Premium will start streaming now.
I hope you can enjoy the show even if you couldn't come to the show.
This was the second Hina Fest for the two of us.
Project's concert. Project concert.
Project concert every time, I get so nervous.
Personally, I think cover songs are the best part of Hina Fest.
I think that cover songs are the best part of HinaFest.
This time I covered JuiceJuice's "Keep On Ascending".
I was so happy to cover JuiceJuice's "Keep On Ascending" this time.
I was so happy and it was fun to dance to it.
It was fun to dance and most of all
It was fun to dance.
I was so happy to be able to perform it.
I was very happy to be able to perform.
I would be happy if you could watch the performance.
And Akari...
Please go!
Let's see...
At the Satosanzanoumi venue
At the event site
I'll be exhibiting my illustrations.
Last year, I exhibited tote bags.
but this year
I drew the usual digital illustrations
I made it under the title of "JuiceJuice Eco House".
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
Yes. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, sir.
yes
Yes ,
We all have JuiceJuice in the house.
They sort the garbage.
Solar panels on the roof, and so on.
The illustrations are all about carbon neutrality, so you can take this opportunity to learn about carbon neutrality.
I hope you will take this opportunity to learn about carbon neutrality.
I hope you will take this opportunity to learn about carbon neutrality, or just take a look at my illustrations.
I drew this illustration so that you can learn about carbon neutrality.
Yes, I've seen it.
I saw it, I saw it, I saw it.
I saw it.
It was good.
It was great.
Thank you.
Hallo! Thank you so much!
So, from the many events that took place at Hina Fest 2024...
I've written down the most impressive songs in my sketchbook.
I'd like to introduce them together.
Seino!
Pan!
Oh! A-ha!
So I, Sakurai, am going to introduce you.
I chose "Sakura Night Fever".
We play this song every year.
During the rehearsal, I was not informed of the special effect of the cherry blossom blizzard.
I wasn't informed of the special effect of the cherry blossom blizzard
I didn't know about it, but it came out of nowhere.
I didn't think it was going to come out, so everyone was like, "Cherry Blossom Few!
Sakura fieu! and it was in the sound of the microphone.
Afterwards, I rewatched the rehearsal video and everyone was so surprised.
"Wow!
It was fun.
And it was really funny that the fans were so surprised too.
But you know what?
The amount of cherry blossoms was amazing.
There were a lot of fans' hearts on the cherry blossoms.
and even the photographer's camera was covered with cherry blossoms.
Wow!
The sun is shining
It's spring
It was also the point where I felt
It was fun!
I performed Berryz KOBO's "Rock Erotic" in the quartet.
I suggested this song.
All of the members had beautiful low tones, so I thought this song would be really cool.
I thought this song would be really cool, so I suggested it.
They all agreed that this song would be the first choice.
It was my personal favorite song, so I was very happy to be able to perform it.
It was really cool and I was so happy to see it offstage.
It was so cool that everyone couldn't stop cheering!
Thank you so much!
By the way, I painted cherry blossoms here.
I am not very good at drawing, so I asked Akari Endo, who also exhibited her illustrations, to draw it for me.
Thank you very much.
And demos Bonus Games
Intuitive
Thank you for your time
I told you for the first time
To all of you who are important to me, don't ever wake up too dreamy and caracara.
Thank you for saying that with such a serious face
I felt a resonance in my heart at that moment.
I'm just waiting for a chance to gather in the morning
Till I make this song echo all over the country
Fly high, fly high, fly high
We'll create our own happiness
With our burdens, we'll reach the endless course of the universe
Countless shutter seashore lands that shine in our hearts
The truck's a heart throb, isn't it?
We, we, we, we, we
With the executive director firmly in tow, the timing is also uneven
Innocent incorrectness, the morning that won't be crushed
Still, it's fun, every day I know
B.A.P.S.C.U.R.A.R.
Unexpected marriage
Someone waiting must be in front of the world
Goosebumps and snakeheads
Tatak princesent mash
With this singing voice
B.A.P.S.C.U.R.A.R.
Shoot back.
Encounter and spread happiness
Everyone is like the shaking of a swaying horse
We are us
Thank you for the chance to meet you
Let's sing from the bottom of our hearts
Don't muddy the tea
We'll cry all the way
It's a singing frenzy
Your hand in mine
Me
me
lalala...
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey...
Yes, so it was the first day of Ochanomama's spring tour with 47 stops in Osaka.
Yes, that's right. Today was the first day of the Osaka performance, and everyone was really excited from the very beginning of the first show. Thank you very much.
Okay, one more comment. Kirara: Yes.
Yes, it was the first day of the tour, so we had new costumes, cute costumes with the colors of the members, and also the Seto was changed a little bit, so I would like you to pay attention to it, I hope you will pay attention to the costumes and the Seto, which were changed a little bit drastically from the previous performance.
Yes, well, then, what is your enthusiasm for the upcoming performances?
Yes, I am. We still have a lot of places to grow, and we really want more people to get to know us, so we will put our heart and soul into each and every performance.
Yes, Kubota.
If it is in my hometown, I would like to go see a live performance of Ocha-no-Ma.
Yes, I think there are many people who are going to see Ochanoma for the first time, so I would like to do my best so that many people will love Ochanoma and want to go to more performances.
Let's extend the tour again so that this spring tour will go well.
Yes, let's all extend it again so that this spring tour will be successful.
So, let's all do our best to complete the Japanese tour of Chutong Prefecture safely.
Yes.
Madoka.
Riri.
Nanami.
Hirano.
Nanomi.
Mire.
Tsube.
Riku.
Yonder.
Side.
Jara jara jara.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll do my best!
Morning Musume。 24's Rio Sakurai and Akari Endo from JuiceJuice. It is time for us to say goodbye.
JuiceJuice will release new single "Tokyo Blur", "Naimono-Love" and "O-aiyoshi" on May 15.
Wow, how exciting!
This is Uemura-san's last single, so please listen to it and check it out.
Also on May 15, Morning Musume。 23 Concert Tour Autumn, "Never Ending Employee Award Special" and "Never Ending Employee Award Sanctuary: Mizuki Fukumura Graduation Special" will be released.
Yes, the tour final was held on two days at Yokohama Arena, and I am sure there will be many points that you will want to see again, so please get these films and watch them over and over again. Please get this film and watch it again.
Please get this film and watch it again. The tour is now underway.
This weekend we will be giving a concert in Sendai.
And the final concert will be held at Nippon Budokan on May 27th.
Please come and see the new Morning Musume。 I would be very happy if you could come to see the tour of Morning Musume。 I am sure you will want to see more of this tour, so please do so.
The Juice Juice Concert Tour 2024 One Line will start on April 20 at the Kanagawa concert.
I am looking forward to it.
The final concert will be held at Nippon Budokan on June 14, so please don't miss the last concert of Uemura-san's last tour.
And, as always, please don't miss the last show of Mr. Uemura's last tour.
From April 19, Hello Project Hina Fest 2024, Juice Juice & Beyones Premium and Tsubaki Factory & Ocha no Uma Premium will start streaming.
I know I talked a lot about memories earlier, but I would be happy if you could pay attention to them as you watch.
I hope you can watch it while paying attention to those memories. Morning Musume。24 will perform at Japan Jam 2024 with Anjelm and BEYONES.
Morning Musume 24 and Angulum will perform on May 3, and BEYONES will perform on May 4.
This will be my first festival this year, so I am really looking forward to it.
So I am really looking forward to it, and at the time of this distribution, there are only three weeks left.
So I am very nervous, but I hope I can enjoy it.
Please come and enjoy the show.
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more.
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time we had Rio Sakurai from Morning Musume 24 and Akari Endo from Juice Juice.
Good-bye.